// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "#include<userdefined.h >Which of the following is the correct syntax to add the header file in the C++ program?",
    answer: "Both A and B",
    options: [
      "#include < userdefined > ",
      "#include \"userdefined.h\"",
      "<include> \"userdefined.h\"",
      "Both A and B"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is the correct syntax to print the message in C++ language?",
    answer: "cout <<\"Hello world!\";",
    options: [
      "cout <<\"Hello world!\";",
      "Cout << Hello world! ;",
      "Out <<\"Hello world!;",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is the correct identifier?",
    answer: "VAR_123",
    options: [
      "$var_name",
      "VAR_123",
      "varname@",
      "None of the above"
      ]
      
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: " Which of the following is the address operator?",
    answer: "&",
    options: [
      "@",
      "#",
      "&",
      "%"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following features must be supported by any programming language to become a pure object-oriented programming language?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Encapsulation",
      "Inheritance",
      "Polymorphism",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
   {
     numb: 6,
     question: "The programming language that has the ability to create new data types is called___.",
     answer: "Extensible",
     options: [
       "Overloaded",
       "Encapsulated",
       "Reprehensible",
       "Extensible"
     ]
   },
    {
     numb: 7,
     question: "Which of the following is the original creator of the C++ language?",
     answer: "Bjarne Stroustrup",
     options: [
       "Dennis Ritchie",
       "Ken Thompson",
       "Bjarne Stroustrup",
       "Brian Kernighan"
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 8,
     question: "The C++ language is ______ object-oriented language.?",
     answer: "Semi Object-oriented or Partial Object-oriented",
     options: [
       "Pure Object oriented",
       "Not Object oriented",
       "Semi Object-oriented or Partial Object-oriented",
       "Both A and B"
     ]
   },
  {
     numb: 9,
     question: "The subclass constructor uses the ———keyword to invoke the constructor of the superclass",
     answer: "Super",
     options: [
       "Super",
       "Final",
       "Static",
       "Public"
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 10,
     question: "Which of the following is a correct way to create an object of class Test? ",
     answer: "Test t=new Test();",
     options: [
       "Test t=new Test();",
       "Test t=new Test;",
       "t=new Test();",
       "new Test t;"
     ]
   },
  

  







];